Defense
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 2\h\h\h\h\h\hMenacing Foul Eight-Legged Beast
"Unwavering One" title acquired
Class: Heavy Knight
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Skills
Grunt Sword
Rampart Reflection
Iron Armor
Titles
Unwavering One
Skill Book
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hAriandype
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Grunt Sword
Iron Armor
Skills
Rampart Reflection
Titles
Unwavering One
Skill Points:
Disarm [Common Skill]
Temporarily reduces the attack of a struck opponent
Poison Beam
Disarm
Flaming Claw
+10% Defense
when holding position
Rampart Reflection
4 skill points acquired
Additional points cannot be added
to Oath of the Heavy Armor at this time.
Oath of the Heavy Armor reached level 15
Parry skill acquired
Status Effect
Poisoned
Rampart Reflection
F-rank
Elymas
Approved
S-rank
A-rank
B-rank
C-rank
D-rank
E-rank
F-rank
Additional points cannot be added
to Oath of the Heavy Armor at this time.
Oath of the Heavy Armor